{
    "subject": "resource/Kingdom_of_Portugal",
    "predicate": "property/governmentType",
    "object": "resource/Constitutional_monarchy",
    "human_readable": "The government type of Kingdom of Portugal is a Constitutional monarchy.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8401391506195068,
            "question": "What type of government does the Kingdom of Portugal have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6443738341331482,
            "question": "Is the Kingdom of Portugal a democracy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5345633625984192,
            "question": "What defines a Constitutional monarchy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4305635690689087,
            "question": "Are there any other countries with a similar government type to Portugal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41793644428253174,
            "question": "What is the role of the constitution in a Constitutional monarchy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3427211344242096,
            "question": "What are the roles and responsibilities of the monarch in a Constitutional monarchy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3308917284011841,
            "question": "Historically, what led to the rise of Constitutional monarchies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26696786284446716,
            "question": "How does a Constitutional monarchy differ from an absolute monarchy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2036541849374771,
            "question": "Can you provide an example of how a Constitutional monarchy balances power?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14761883020401,
            "question": "What are some potential advantages and disadvantages of a Constitutional monarchy?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The government type of Kingdom of Portugal is a Constitutional monarchy.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8739_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide an example of how a Constitutional monarchy balances power?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8739_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does a Constitutional monarchy differ from an absolute monarchy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8739_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Historically, what led to the rise of Constitutional monarchies?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8739_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8739_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8739_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8739_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8739_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8739_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8739_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8739_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8739_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8739_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8739_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you'd like to evaluate more triples! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all the documents mention that Portugal is a constitutional monarchy, and one of them even explains what this means. There is no information provided that contradicts this fact."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"The government type of Kingdom of Portugal is a Constitutional monarchy.\" For instance, several documents mention that Portugal operates under a constitutional parliamentary monarchy and details about the role of the monarch being limited by a constitution and acting as a figurehead."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}